

# Adrijan Sulejmanov

FullStack Developer

#### Summerize

Experienced developer seeking for full time and detail-oriented Web Developer with a knack for conceptualizing and delivering elegant, user-friendly solutions effectively and efficiently. Have 8 years of experience as a Full Stack Developer, specialized in Modern JS and PHP frameworks. Love to collaborate with team actively, growing myself to make a blade of team and business.nd part time engagements.

# **Key Competencies**

- Team Collaboration
- Debugging skills
- Meeting Deadline correctly
- Responsive
- Self management

#### Contact me at:

Email: andrysoul32@gmail.com Address: 26 Crnook, Skopje 1000, North Macedonia

## **Work History**

### FullStack Developer

Freelancing, Self Employed| Jan 2020 - Dec 2020

- Frontend:
- ReactJS with Redux-thunk & Redux-Saga, Apollo GraphQL, GraphQL-Yoga, React-Context, React-RestHook, and Typescript
- HTML5, CSS3 & Bootstrap, SCSS, Material UI & Design
- .
- Backend:
- Node, Express, Loopback, Hapi, Laravel, Symfony, Yii2, Python
- •
- Database:
- MongoDB, MySQL, PostgreSQL, Redis
- •
- DevOps:
- Jenkins CICD Pipelines
- Docker, Docker Swarm
- Kubernetes
- AWS, GCP & Azure

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Asolvi Mar 2018 - Dec 2019

- Built shipping Single page Applications and brought delightful user interactions.
- Have worked with Redux and Reframe as a state management libraries.
- Built cross-platform application, backend services and open platform with team.
- Improve previous code qualities, define architecture on database newly and implemented enough unit testing with Mocha.
- Archived well-tested solutions, high-qualities, maintainable and scalable characteristics.
- Integrated a Cloud Firestore database with an existing codebase.
- Developed a controller service that is deployed in Heroku. It turns on and off the GPU server to save money, communicates with the diacritizer, and interfaces with the front-end app.
- Developed an admin panel with sophisticated client-side state management that enabled a manufacturing company's admins to create and monitor jobs and parts manufactured along with an employee management system.
- Developed a Node.js API service and handled its deployment as well as the deployment of a MongoDB database

#### **Tech Skills**

- JS / TS | PHP | Python
- React / Redux / Context API / Mobx / Apollo / hooks
- Yii2 / Symfony / Laravel / CodeIgniter
- Django / Flask
- JHipster / Spring Boot
- AWS: EC2 / Lambda / Fargate / ECS / SNS & SQS / RDS

## **Key Skills**

- Creative and Building Frontend Page
- TDD/BDD
- Web & Cross-platform development
- Fast Turnaround
- Github / GitFlow

#### Full Stack Developer

Consalata Mar 2016 - Feb 2018

- Created an API for a sports related mobile app using a Slim framework. Built an event promoting site in Symfony4 with heavy usage of a Cloudinar y API for image processing.
- Developed a real-time video streaming solution with various billing options, using Symfony2, Wowza Media Server, Redis and NodeJS.
- Created an online advice web solution prepared for law companies; basically, it is a web form that could be implemented on every web page and allows users to request legal advice. The bigger part of the project was administration panel that allows law companies to manage the advice requests, a manual and automatic internal email system, and payment solutions.

#### **Full Stack Developer**

Saburly Feb 2014 - Feb 2016

- Developed responsive mobile web applications with AngularJS.
- Mentored experienced developers who were new to JavaScript.
- Analyzed front-end technological options (CSS frameworks, Protractor, design patterns, and more) and helped the team settle upon our technology foundation.
- Led the development of Sears eCoupon application with a similar criteria and oversaw its deployment and integration with Sears' subsidiary domains.d oversaw its deployment and integration with Sears' subsidiary domains.

## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

## University American College Skopje

Bachelor's degree | 2010- 2014

- Software development
- Web programming and Management Database